<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!DOCTYPE xbel
	PUBLIC "+//IDN python.org//DTD XML Bookmark Exchange Language 1.0//EN//XML" "http://pyxml.sourceforge.net/topics/dtds/xbel-1.0.dtd">
<xbel version="1.0">
  <title>Supporting Software</title>

  <desc>Some supporting software is provided as part of the Python XML
  "omnibus" package. This software is located in the demo/xbel/ directory of
  the distribution. This includes command-line processes for converting XBEL
  instances to other common formats, including the Navigator and Internet
  Explorer formats. The following bookmarks refer to other XBEL
  software.</desc>

  <folder>
    <title>Bookmark Synchronization and Merging</title>

    <bookmark href="http://xbel.sourceforge.net/2006/XBELicious/">
      <title>XBELicious</title>

      <desc>XBELicious is a set of scripts to help you store your
      del.icio.us bookmarks in XBEL format and to mold those bookmarks into
      a hierarchy of folders based partly upon the tags that you have given
      to those bookmarks.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://bookmarkbridge.sourceforge.net/">
      <title>BookmarkBridge</title>

      <desc>Ken Schenke's BookmarkBridge is an open source bookmark
      management tool. It is used to merge bookmarks from different
      browsers, and uses Python for at least a portion of it's regression
      testing.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://aspn.activestate.com/ASPN/Cookbook/Python/Recipe/135131">
      <title>Python Recipe: Merging XBEL Bookmark Files</title>

      <desc>Merging XBEL Bookmark files, by Uche Ogbuji, is a Python recipe
      for merging 2 XBEL files.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://www.collaboration-world.com/cgi-bin/collaboration-world/project/index.cgi?pid=1/">
      <title>XBELette</title>

      <desc>XBELette, a "Client-server solution for managing your
      bookmarks".</desc>
    </bookmark>
  </folder>

  <folder>
    <title>XBEL-Aware Web Browsers and Web Browser Plugins</title>

    <bookmark href="http://galeon.sourceforge.net/">
      <title>Galeon</title>

      <desc>The Galeon Web browser for the GNOME desktop  has been using
      XBEL as its native bookmark format since version 1.1.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://grail.sourceforge.net/">
      <title>Grail Internet Browser</title>

      <desc>The current release of the  Grail Internet browser from CNRI
      supports XBEL as a native bookmarks format.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://www.konqueror.org/">
      <title>Konqueror</title>

      <desc>David Faure (faure@kde.com) has made XBEL the bookmarks format
      for Konqueror, the KDE web browser since KDE 2.1. KDE also features a
      separate application to edit XBEL bookmarks, keditbookmarks.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://elinks.or.cz/">
      <title>ELinks</title>

      <desc>ELinks, ad advanced text WWW browser, has built-in XBEL
      bookmarks support. Basic bookmarks operations (same as in the native
      format) and conversion from/to native ELinks' bookmarks format.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="">
    </bookmark>
  </folder>

  <folder>
    <title>General Bookmark Tools</title>

    <bookmark href="http://www.linkagogo.com/">
      <title>linkaGoGo</title>

      <desc>linkaGoGo is a commercial online bookmark/favorites "service"
      which supports import and export in several formats, including
      XBEL.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://www.url-manager.com/">
      <title>URL Manager Pro</title>

      <desc>Alco Blom's URL Manager Pro, a Mac OS shareware application for
      managing bookmarks, supports reading files in the XBEL format. See the
      home page of URL Manager Pro for more information.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://www.favorez.com/xml">
      <title>Favorez</title>

      <desc>Favorez is an AxtiveX IE 5+ plug-in program that creates web
      pages from the users' favorites. It uses XBEL, and includes an XSLT
      stylsheet for converting XBEL to a dynamic folder-based view.</desc>
    </bookmark>
  </folder>

  <folder>
    <title>Support for Other Tools</title>

    <bookmark href="http://www.giungato.it/">
      <title>A PHP Script to Parse XBEL and a Compass Template that
      Maintains Foldering Information</title>

      <desc>Roberto Giungato (roberto.giungato@its.it) has created a PHP
      script to parse XBEL and a Compass template that maintains foldering
      information. See his home page for more information.</desc>
    </bookmark>

    <bookmark href="http://gazonk.org/~eloj/projects/operatoxbel.html">
      <title>Opera to XBEL</title>

      <desc>OperaToXBEL.py is a Python script for converting Opera bookmarks
      to XBEL, by Eddy L O Jansson.</desc>
    </bookmark>
  </folder>

</xbel>
